mp3converter.net 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy - Mp3Converter.net

### Privacy Policy

#### 1\. Privacy

Privacy has become the primary concern on the internet. Mp3converter is very strict in sharing personal information of our users. This privacy articulation describes how Mp3converter.net accords with your information. By accessing this site, you are accepting the practices mention in this privacy statements.

We believe that privacy of your personal information is crucial.mp3converter is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

Our policy illustrate on this page expresses that the personal information received from you will be processed by us.

Please read our privacy policies carefully to understand our views and practices regarding the utilization of your personal data.

Based on your information we enable you with certain features to exemplify understanding on the website.

#### 2\. IP Address cookies

Almost several online applications use cookies. We do use cookies for tracking the information of our users. A cookie is actually a small file of letters and numbers that will be put onto your computer only with your permission. Once you agree the file is added and the cookie helps you analyze web traffic or let you know when you visit a particular site.Mp3converter.net does not require you to disclose personal information anywhere on the site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting patterns. 

It transfers the information between the main site and your computer which your accessing. They are stored in the special folder in your temporary internet files directory.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or finds a unique “cookie” on your browser. It monitors the efficiency of the website and monitors accumulated metrics such as the number of visitors and page views.

We may assemble your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. 

If you do not want to have a cookie set when visiting our website, you are permitted to change the settings in your browser or by managing preferences in programs in order to get rid of the cookies. Well, after applying that you may not be able to have full access to some of our pages.

#### 3\. Collected Information

First of all, note that we may collect and process some basic information for providing information for providing an eligible product. Information is to store and monitor and analyze service quality. We do not collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal address, email addresses etc. you may be asked to reveal certain information such as your email address to advertisers, third-party entities, or a mailing list administrator .you are solely responsible for submitting critical information of yours, at your own discretion. It is neither collected nor stores by [Mp3converter.net](https://www.mp3converter.net/).

#### 4\. Advertising

We allow third-party companies to serve up ads and/or collect certain unidentified information when you visit our website. These companies may use private identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, a subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) when you visit this and other Web sites for advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies distinctively use a cookie or third party external reference to grab this intelligence

#### 5\. Distribution of Information

We may share information with the governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when we are asked by the governmental authorities. Prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions.

#### 6\. Privacy Contact Information

If you have any queries or comments about our privacy policy or your dealings with the website, please contact us at ([ [email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#daa9afaaaab5a8ae9ab7aae9b9b5b4acbfa8aebfa8f4b4bfae) )
